Jingyan.
Why is it you?
What are you doing at my house?
I brought you guys some fruit.
Wait,
what are you two doing here?
Us...
We...
We were going to cook.
Right.
Cooking.
And then,
the power tripped.
Right.
It tripped.
Tripped.
Cooking?
You two?
That's a first.
Shiya and I are getting divorced soon.
She will move out in a couple of days.
I asked her to teach me how to cook a few dishes,
afraid I'll starve to death.
Pei Song,
if you had realized this earlier,
you wouldn't be getting a divorce.
Let me tell you,
many people say
if you want to capture someone's heart...
You have to win her stomach.
It doesn't mean you have to know how to cook everything,
but rather when you are cooking,
you can have some physical contact.
For example,
when cutting vegetables,
you cut your finger.
When frying,
oil splashes on you.
Or you can tie each other's aprons.
It's not about making you a chef.
And,
we women value men and women working together,
making the work less tiring.
What we want is this sense of security.
Sense of security.
Who told you to be here?
Of course,
if you can cook,
that's even better.
Right?
Shiya.
Is your mom feeling better lately?
Keep your voice down.
Why hasn't she told you yet?
What did you say happened to Shiya's mom?
Let Shiya tell you herself.
I'm leaving now.
Go ahead.
Behave yourself.
What happened to your mom?
Shiya.
Please save your brother.
Your brother is dying.
Your brother owes a lot of money.
They kidnapped your brother.
They said if he can't pay back the money,
they'll make him a scapegoat.
Aren't you the daughter-in-law of the Pei family?
Only you can save him.
I already saved him once.
I've paid for his mistakes too.
He brought this all on himself.
I'm incompetent.
I can't save him.
You should call the police.
How can you be so cold-blooded?
Song Shiya.
We shouldn't have
given birth to you.
Cold-blooded?
When you stole my identity
to borrow from loan sharks for him,
why didn't you say you shouldn't have given birth to me?
Shiya.
Mom.
Mom,
Shiya,
I'm begging you.
Save him one last time, please?
Mom.
Do you want your mother to kill herself right in front of you?
Please save your brother.
If you don't save him,
we will expose your contract marriage
with the Pei family.
Let's see how the Pei family handles that.
How can you be so shameless?
Shiya.
Don't be angry.
Your father was just too anxious,
that's why he said that.
We have no other choice.
You are a good child.
You won't just stand by and watch your brother die, right?
Just save him this one last time, okay?
He was just trying to make money to pay off his debts.
He was momentarily blinded
and participated in that big data analysis experiment.
We didn't expect them
to all be scammers.
Your brother's debt
just kept growing.
Here is some money I saved up before.
Take it back and pay it off first.
I will arrange temporary housing for you later.
For now, just don't go out running around.
Wait for me to contact you.
Understand?
Hello, Mom.
Shiya,
Song Shiya.
Your brother committed suicide.
After my brother passed away,
Dad tried to get an explanation from those people,
running around,
but got into a car accident.
Mom couldn't take the shock
and lost her mind.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know about any of this.
From now on,
you won't be alone anymore.
But
I suspect things aren't that simple.
So I've been investigating for the past six months,
and I found out that Pei Ning is involved.
I know he's always had feelings for me,
so I used that to get close to him
to find out what he was up to.
I discovered he's been developing
an AI algorithm.
But if this algorithm
falls into the wrong hands,
there's a huge risk of personal privacy leaks.
So,
is that why you wanted a divorce?
That was the only way
he would drop his guard around me,
so I could gather more evidence.
But if you do this,
you could be in danger.
Aren't you afraid?
If
fate can't be changed
and I'm destined to die,
then I'll accept it.
But until then,
I absolutely won't just sit around and wait for it.